

<u>bodron.beatris@gmail.com</u>

+(40)757 539 984

## **Profile**

Hi! I am Beatrice and I am an organized person. I'm always creating new ideas, new ways of doing things and I'm self-motivated, hard-working individual. I like to dance, to walk my dog, to paint, to do sports and to experience new activities. Also, I've been trying to improve my programming skills for the couple of months in order to become a web developer

## **Creative Works**

#### **Bachelor Degree Project, Cluj-Napoca**

February 2020 — December 2020

- for my senior thesis i wanted to recondition and improve the interface of the existing site of my University, as well as to achieve a better functionalty of the electronic catalogs.
- to create the interface i used HTML,CSS and for functionality, i used JavaScript and JSON data.
- the creation of the site was done using VisualCode and involved the following steps: creating a modern interface, easy to understand and access by the user, with clear elements to facilitate navigation within the app, protection of personal data by presence of the two factors login page, the connection between the local JSON data server and my app, so that we can edit the fields of notes specific to each student, as well as save those changes via a button. At the same time, by using the Bootstrap framework, i've managed to create a dynamic site, with responsive elements, which changes its order / dimensions depending on the size of the display, so regardless of the device the app is accessed, the site will display a clean interface. Also, the navbar, when the dimension of the display is medium or small, becomes a droplist.

## **Experience**

### Practice, S.C. ROBERT BOSCH SRL, Cluj-Napoca

July 2019 — August 2019

- START Project
- MFC-t department
- I've created and VBA application for the department i was in

#### Volunteer, Targul de Cariere in IT, Cluj-Napoca

March 2019 — March 2019

- elobs stand.
- I've generated the QR codes for the people with eJobs accounts. Also, i've created new profiles for the ones that didn't have one.

**Engineering Summer University, Organizatia Studentilor Universitatii Tehnice, Cluj-Napoca**July 2015 — July 2015

- student for two weeks
- I've participated to all the presentations made by every faculty of the Technical University of Cluj
- I've been to classes and i've understood what is like to be a student at this University
- I've participated to all the group activites like: treasure hunt, board games

### Volunteer, Organizatia " Initiativa Tinerilor", Targu-Neamt

May 2013 — June 2014

- Volunteering Department of the Targu-Neamt Police .
- Topic: Combating violence

# **Education and Training**

### REACT JS: LEARN REACT JS FROM SCRATCH WITH HANDS-ON PROJECTS, Udemy

September 2021 — October 2021

https://www.udemy.com/course/react-learn-react-js-from-scratch-with-hands-on-projects/

### THE COMPLETE JAVASCRIPT COURSE, Udemy

June 2021 — Present

https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-javascript-course/learn/lecture/22648961?start=570#content

### THE WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP 2021, Udemy

February 2021 — June 2021

https://www.udemy.com/course/the-web-developer-bootcamp/learn/lecture/22052726?start=0#content

# BACHELOR DEGREE, Faculty of Electronics Telecommunications and Information Tehnology, Cluj-Napoca

October 2016 — February 2021

- Applied Electronics

### DIPLOMA BACALAUREAT, Colegiul National Stefan cel Mare, Targu-Neamt

September 2012 — June 2016

Profile: Mathematics-Informatics

### Skills

HTML	CSS
JavaScript	REACT
Bootstrap	Express.js
JSON	GitHub
Languages	
English	Spanish
French	